[MUSIC]
[음악]
We've built a simple model just relating square feet of living space to price
전용면적과 주택 가격의 관계를 나타내는 간단한 모델을 세워봤고
of houses and then we explored some other features like zip codes,
우편번호, 우편번호가 크게 좌지우지하는 건 확실하죠,
and it's clear the zip codes make a big difference and there's other features,
침실, 이것도 크죠, 과 같은 특징을
bedrooms, that also makes a big difference.
살펴보았습니다
The question is can we get a better model by including more features, more of these?
중요한 점은 특징을 더 추가함으로써 모델을 향상시킬 수 있냐는 것입니다
And so let's look at that.
한번 살펴보죠
So we're gonna do here is build
이제부터 할 건
a regression model with more features.
회귀 모델 특징 추가하기입니다
So this is using this bigger feature set that we just described.
방금 설명드린 것보다 더 큰 특징 세트를 활용합니다
So the first one I called the sqft_model.
첫 번째는 sqft_model이라 했습니다
Let's call this
이걸
the my_features_model.
my_features_model이라 명명합니다
So the my_features_model is again going to take graphlab.linear regression.create.
my_features_model은 다시 graphlab.linear_regression.create에
So we're gonna create it and we're gonna use the training data,
훈련 데이터를 입력 받습니다
just like we did before.
전에 했던 것처럼요
Our target is again going to be the price, just like before.
대상은 전과 같이 가격이 될 겁니다
However, the features here that I'm gonna use are going to be those
하지만 특징은
features that are called my features which I created earlier.
방금 생성한 my_features를 쓸 겁니다
So let's go and execute this.
실행해보죠
So now I use more features and it's straining and I think it's done it's done.
더 많은 특징들을 사용했고 죽죽 나오네요 다 된 것 같습니다
Using those, I forget how many, eight features.
8개의 특징을 사용했습니다
I use, let's just print them out here, print my_features.
뭘 썼는지 my_features를 출력해봅시다
So I use bedrooms, bathrooms,
침실, 화장실,
square foot of living, square foot of lot, floors and zip code.
전용면적, 대지면적, 층수, 우편번호네요
Now we have two models.
이제 모델이 두 갭니다
We have the sqft_model and we have my_features_model.
sqft_model과 my_features_model이지요
How do they compare in terms of performance?
성능으로 비교하면 어떨까요?
So here's what I'm going to do.
이렇게 하죠
I'm going to print the sqft_model.evaluate,
sqft_model.evaluate이
evaluate all my test data.
모든 테스트 데이터를 평가하죠
And I'm also going to print
그 다음 my_features_model.evaluate을
the my_features_model.evaluate on the same test data.
똑같은 테스트 데이터에 실행합니다
And let's compare, let's see what happened.
어떻게 되는지 보죠
Okay, so to start with,
살펴보면
we saw that the biggest error in the simple square foot model was $4 million.
간단한 평수 모델의 가장 큰 오류는 400만입니다
Now it's down to $3.4 million, 49, so 3.5 million.
밑에 건 340만이네요, 49니까 350만이라고 하죠
So it went down a bit.
약간 내려갔습니다
And root mean squared error, the average error,
RMSE, 평균 오류는 25.5만에서
went down from $255,000 as we had over here to a $179,000.
17.9만으로 내려갔습니다
Now, if you add more and more features, your area is likely going to decrease
특징을 추가하면 할수록 오류가 줄어들 확률이
quite a bit more because there's quite a bit of data here and
높은데 데이터가 일단 많고
there's lots that you can learn.
아직 학습할 거리가 많기 때문이죠
But again, just adding some extra features already helped us with our performance.
다시 말하지만 몇몇 특징을 추가한 것만으로도 성능이 올라갔습니다
[MUSIC]
[음악]